<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<androidx.constraintlayout.widget.ConstraintLayout xmlns:android="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res/android"
    xmlns:app="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res-auto"
    xmlns:tools="http://schemas.android.com/tools"
    android:layout_width="match_parent"
    android:layout_height="match_parent"
    tools:context=".MainActivity2">

    <ScrollView
        android:layout_width="match_parent"
        android:layout_height="match_parent"
        android:scrollbarSize="10dp">

        <LinearLayout
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:orientation="vertical">

            <TextView
                android:layout_width="match_parent"
                android:layout_height="1220dp"
                android:padding="16dp"
                android:text="DISCLAIMER: The creator of this app is not a registered psychologist
in any way, shape, or form. The results you obtain from these questionnaires do not
serve as diagnoses to personality disorders, rather they're intentions are to depict
the likelihood one may need to seek help from professionals. \n\nAnti-social personality
disorder (ASPD) is characterized by rash, impulsive, irresponsible and negligent
behaviour. A person with ASPD can be manipulative, deceitful, reckless, and lack
empathy. Psychopaths and sociopaths tend to fall into this category. \n\nNarcissistic
personality disorder (NPD) is a mental health condition characterized by having
excessive grandiosity and vanity of oneself. People with NPD seek excessive
validation and admiration from their peers. Often mistaken for psychopaths due to
their ego-centrism. People with NPD can be manipulative and often become extremely
hostile when upset, due to their deep-seeded insecurities and low self-esteem.
\n\nBorderline personality disorder (BPD) is characterized by having an intense fear of
abandonment, and difficulty tolerating being alone. Severely impacting one's
ability to manage their emotions, a person with BPD tends to be rash and impulsive.
Usually, during times of great distress, a person with BPD may partake in reckless
and dangerous behaviors like binge-eating, reckless driving, casual sex, and
substance abuse.\n\nHistrionic personality disorder (HPD) or commonly known as a
dramatic personality disorder, is a psychiatric disorder distinguished by a
pattern of exaggerated emotionality and attention-seeking behaviors.
Ones with HPD are typically flirtatious, seductive, charming, manipulative,
impulsive, and lively."
                android:textSize="20sp"
                android:textStyle="bold" />

            <LinearLayout
                android:layout_width="350dp"
                android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                android:orientation="horizontal"
                android:layout_gravity="center">

                <Button
                    android:id="@+id/backButton"
                    android:layout_width="100dp"
                    android:layout_height="55dp"
                    android:layout_marginEnd="80dp"
                    android:layout_weight="1"
                    android:text="BACK"
                    android:textSize="16sp"
                    android:textStyle="bold"
                    tools:ignore="ButtonStyle" />

                <Button
                    android:id="@+id/nextButton"
                    android:layout_width="100dp"
                    android:layout_height="55dp"
                    android:layout_weight="1"
                    android:text="NEXT"
                    android:textSize="16sp"
                    android:textStyle="bold"
                    tools:ignore="ButtonStyle" />
            </LinearLayout>
        </LinearLayout>
    </ScrollView>

</androidx.constraintlayout.widget.ConstraintLayout>
